My dear old Papa discovered
this mummy years ago.
Then we found this ancient
virus still inside.
That was Asmodeus?
Perhaps! Could also have
been Beelzebub!
S.T.G. would create a pandemic!?
Of course!
Then, using the panacea created
from MJ and Asmodeus,
S.T.G. would sell the cure and
become the richest in the world!
You monster!!
To be honest, I don't even
care about the medicine!
A new race of humans shall be
born that will rule over all!
All according to Asmodeus's Legend.
Won't everyone just die!?
Those with the ancient
DNA shall live!
Then that means...
Yes!
To fulfill the legend, I created
that Ryo from the mummy's DNA!
What!?
Ryo might have been a failure, but
he still lead me to MJ in the end!
I'm eternally grateful.
You're a cruel man!
A cruel man who will control
humanity's fate!
Someone's got to accept the burden!