Ugh! It's so rancid!!
What's this SMELL!?
Oh god, it's so gross!!
Are you okay, Misato!?
Look! There's someone inside!
Ryo!
No way!
Hajime! Tomowo! Run!
Get out of here now!!
You know, it was a pain in the ass
keeping you guys in
the dark this long.
Director Tenma!
Director? Like, the hospital's?
My other face is an agent
of S.T.G.
What!? S.T.G.!?
Huh!?
It's a top-class research group.
They trapped the five of us
here for their plan.
Plan?
The Asmos Legend.
Do you know of it?
The legend of ancient
evolved humans?
That's right.
S.T.G. has researched this legend
and has finally unraveled the puzzle.
Asmos referred to a person
with the perfect antibodies.
Antibodies?
A system that protects the body
from infection.
With perfect Asmos cells,
we could cure any and
all ailments in the world.
That's impossible!
The ancient virus and a person
with the perfect DNA.
With these, it's certainly
possible, Kisaragi.
All this for THAT!?
The ancient Asmodeus virus
is right here.
Within me.
Then, the one's with perfect
DNA are--!
Precisely. The perfect DNA, MJ.
The MJ exists amongst you.
We couldn't find MJ even after
countless experiments.
BUT!!! MJ finally graced us
with its presence...
How could you be sure?
We were able to determine that
MJ existed in this region,
so we set up a hospital, where we
could get thousands of DNA samples.
Then finally, we found you guys.
Don't you think it's the perfect hiding
place for this research?
No one would think more
of an outbreak or two.
And you call yourself a doctor!?
All that matters is finding MJ as
soon as possible!
Robert, begin!
Yes, sir!